

Aleksandar Tanevski

E-mail : aleksandar.tanevski@outlook.com

Website: https://atanevski.github.io
Mobile MK: +389 75 43 68 13

Mobile NL +31 6556 06 364 available until 5 July 17'

.

Skype : <u>aleksandar.tanevski@outlook.com</u>

LinkedIn: https://mk.linkedin.com/in/aleksandartanevski Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aleksandartanes

Personal statement

I am 25 years old with 2+ years of working experience both in Front-end and Back-end development and currently in my last year of studies affaculty of Computer Science and Engineering in Skopje, soon to be "Bachelor of Engineering (Information technologies)".

Through my collage and work experience, I have worked on various technologies

- ASP.NET MVC with Entity Framework both Code-First and DB-First, WEB API 2, JavaScript, JQuery, Bootstrap, AJAX, HTML5, CSS3 excellent knowledge
- Azure Service Bus, Azure Webjobs, SQL, Linq, Node.js, MongoDB, UML Diagrams, TypeScript working knowledge
- Unit testing, Angular.js, Python, Semantic Web, LESS, SASS -basic knowledge
- API Integrations Google, Facebook, Hubspot, Pipedrive, GoDaddy, Stripe
- IDEs, Text Editors, Helpers Visual Studio, Visual Studio Code, Microsoft SQL Management Studio, ReSharper, Postman, PhoneGap
- Project Tracking and other knowledge JIRA, Asana, Trello, Agile Scrum, Slack, Rapid Application Development, Git, TFS
- Languages English (Fluent)

Also I have directly participated in software architecture planning, creating onboarding, recruiting and Management processes and procedures.

I am hardworking, team player, dedicated, loyal, passionate about new technologies also highly motivated and interested in researching solutions to problems. I grasp new concepts and ideas quickly, highly ambitious and tend to always achieve my plans and goals.

I declare myself as #JUNIORDEVFORLIFE because you never stop learning.

Work experience

Self-employed

Professional Freelancer

February 2017 — Present

- Back-end Development ASP.NET MVC, ASP.NET Web Api 2, Azure Service bus, Azure WebJobs Multi-threaded applications, Consultant Software Architecture
- Front-end development Bootstrap, CSS 3, JQuery, Ajax, Mustache, Alpaca.js, TypeScript
- CRM and ERP API Integrations (Hubspot, PipeDrive, SalesForce), Database modeling and realization MSSQL

iVote Dec 2016 — Jan 2017

Full-stack Web Developer

- Back-end Development ASP.NET MVC with custom multi tier architecture
- Front-end development Bootstrap, CSS 3, JQuery, Ajax, Mustache, TypeScript
- Database modeling and realization MSSQL, Stored procedures, Optimizations
- Research and development

ITCrowd Feb 2016 — Nov 2016

Full-stack Web Developer

- Development software and web solutions
- Back-end Development ASP.NET MVC with Entity Framework,
- NodeJS(express), MongoDB
- Front-end development Bootstrap, CSS 3, JQuery
- Cordova cross platform experience (Phonegap) JS, CSS, HTML5
- Developing RESTful APIs
- Database modeling and realization MSSQL
- Research and development
- Managing and tutoring interns
- Involved in designing software solutions
- Involved in designing on boarding and recruitment processes

Self-employed Sep 2013 — Feb 2016

Private Tutor

- Preparing students for faculty exams
- Computer Organization and Design (Computer Arithmetic, Error-detecting codes, MIPS)
- Logic boards (Logic gates, Flip Flops, Coders, Decoders, Multiplexers and its applications)
- Algorithms (Java Collection, Synchronizations, Basic algorithms (Bubble sort, Iterating arrays)

- Front end development (CSS, HTML5, JQuery, JavaScript)
- Object oriented programming (C++, Java, C#)
- Structured programming (C)

Freelance

Jun 2015 — Feb 2016

Freelancer

Freelancing as a Front-end Developer where most of the projects were customizing websites. By customizing is meant responsive designs using Bootstrap and some JS/JQuery scripts, adding plugins, features and animations with JQuery and JQuery UI, AJAX async calls, DataTables and CSS3 improvements.

Projects

SoPro.io

Lead Generation Portal

- Marketing intranet Web Application for company that works Lead generation.
- CRUD operations for campaigns, prospects, agents, user roles etc., where the accent, the complexity is on the User Experience, Database Modeling and Relationships. Data reports
- Real-time dashboards, calculating and exporting raw data to Excel, Pdf, Csv formats
- Used technologies ASP.NET MVC, Azure SQL, Azure, JavaScript, JQuery, MSSQL, AJAX, HTML

GetItGone.co.uk

Lead Generation Portal

- · Web solution for selling your car which connects with multiple selling dealers for best price.
- Used technologies ASP.NET MVC, ASP.NET Web API 2, Azure SQL, Azure, JavaScript, JQuery, MSSQL, AJAX, HTML

iVote.mk

Demokra - electoral software

- Web solution for electoral process in Macedonia
- Used technologies ASP.NET MVC, Razor, JavaScript, JQuery, MSSQL

www.MediawireMobile.com

Cross Platform Publishing

- Publish your own magazines, newspaper, or book conveniently online. MediaWire Solutions turns your unique image and branding into a marketable medium for
 your clients and customers. We give publishers a way to represent their brand and products, expand their media presence and generate dynamic information
 about visitors and customers with our Digital Publishing Software that generates native branded apps on ios and android for Phones and Tablets.
- My objectives were mostly bug fixing, improvements and payment processors (Stripe API)
- Used technologies Node.JS (express), MongoDB

UEFA Euro predictor

Web Application

- Web Based Application for predicting UEFA Euro 2016 from Group Stage to Final match. The player(client) predicts and interactively choose the first 3
 representations for each UEFA group. When he/she confirms the selection another screen appears to choose which 3rd placed representations proceed into
 elimination phase. The next screen is to choose the winner and enter predicted score for each bracket match. After the UEFA Euro Championship ended there
 was simple parser for the data which filtered the clients that predicted well.
- Used technologies ASP.NET MVC, MSSQL, Bootstrap, JQuery, JavaScript, HTML5, CSS3

>www.AmigoAmigo.nl , www.Deal123.nl

E-Commerce website

- E-Commerce site where the objective of the project is to allow the user to buy products for lower prices and to apply for jobs.
- My objectives were mostly bug fixing and updating the Facebook API
- Used technologies ASP.NET MVC, JavaScript, JQuery, MSSQL, AJAX, HTML

SOYAL and other RFID - Card readers

WPF and Web

- Access control management system for Id card/tag readers. The solution is with multi-tier architecture where the base layer is the communication with the card
 readers via serial (rs-485) communication with custom DAL. The desktop application is only for controlling and programming the card readers.
- The other part of the project is presenting the data and generating reports which is via with Web portal which communicates with the same database.
- $\bullet \quad \text{Used technologies WPF, ASP.NET MVC, SQL, JavaScript, JQuery, MSSQL, HTML, CSS}\\$

Company Product

Web Api

• The project is B2B platform where helps one business to order goods or services from other business. This solution automatizes the process with digital signing

- and archiving the documentation and also notifies the producer, the seller and the buyer about the order.
- Used technologies ASP.NET Web Api 2 with Entity Framework, MSSQL

2D Game Application

Cross platform game

- Multiplayer Cross platform app with multiple 2D Games such as Quiz, Risk (board game) and interactive "restaurant-waiter" game with multiple characters and animations. *Undisclosed app
- Used technologies ASP.NET SignalR, Cordova (PhoneGap), JavaScript, HTML5, CSS

Hackathon - Code Up Level Up

Windows Phone app - Ordering food

• Team project - Windows Phone 7 application which allows the user to order food from restaurants with food delivery service in Skopje, Macedonia. After choosing a restaurant, the user makes order from the menu of the restaurant. The delivery location was provided by the gps sensor of the device and the payment via credit

Hackathon - CodeCamp

Game engine

Faculty of computer science and engineering

Faculty projects and courses

- Web based systems (RDF, RDFS, OWL, Semantic Web)
 - Linked data Java swing application which lists medicine from Health Insurance Fund of Macedonia (Turtle format base) and all prices from Europe of the same medicine
- Java script
 - o Simple family tree Interactive template that allows user to generate family tree
- Visual programming C#
 - o Simple image viewer using Windows Forms
- Advanced Programming Java
- Python Programming
- Windows forms
- ASP.NET
- · Advanced web development
 - o JS, Bootstrap, CSS
 - o Team project Front-end for Cisco Macedonia website
- SQL Database
- CCNA Cisco Certified Network Associate

Education

Computer Science 2011 — Present

Faculty of Computer Science and Engineering Bachelor of Engineering (Information Technologies)

High School 2008 — 2011

St. Clement of Ohrid